feedster.com 2007-06-07

# Feedster Privacy Policy

**About Feedster**  
Feedster allows organizations and individuals to harness the rich quantity of information available in today's ever growing selection of RSS feeds and weblogs.  Feedster, developer of the most powerful RSS search engine, offers the easiest and most robust way to take advantage of this timely content. To fulfill the purpose of this site, some personal information we ask for is used for communication purposes to our subscribers.

**Privacy Policy Summary**  
Feedster strives to maintain and protect personally identifiable information about users internally, as detailed in our privacy policy below. We will only share aggregated statistical information not tied to personally identifiable information with partners and vendors, in order to improve our internal business processes and serve better information to our customers.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Feedster is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Feedster collects information from its users at several different points on its Web site. You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We use cookies to link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so to improve the information we present and our other internal business processes.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and if we disclose it. If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**  
Feedster users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as preferences and Account Info.

**Registration**  
In order to use the subscription areas of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (name and email address) and to create a username & password. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Feedster does not require the user to provide demographic information, such as income level and gender, nor unique identifiers such as social security number.

**Privacy for Minors**  
Feedster does not knowingly collect personal data from children as they use the site. If you would like us to override this, please contact us to obtain parent or guardian approval. Read below for more information on the Online Child Protection Act.

**Use of Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a session cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Web site, unless a member is logged into the site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Web site, a subscriber would not have to log in with a password, thereby saving time each time they visit our site. Should the user want to temporarily disable this function they can do so by clicking the log-out link, at which point the login cookie will be deleted. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.  Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site and improve our internal business processes.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are linked to personally identifiable information sometimes.

**Sharing**  
Feedster does not share subscription information about individuals with anyone, except as stated here. Log data is maintained and used for our internal business processes, and this information is shared only in aggregate with our partners and vendors, or as required by law.

If users choose to display their subscription information because they have claimed a blog, their user name, blog(s) and member photos will be shown as associated with their blog to other users on the site. Subscribers who do not claim weblogs will never have their subscription information shown or attached to a blog on the external website. Any subscriber's information including other information from the subscription form or any emailed information we receive from members, will not be shared outside the company, except as aggregated statistics, or as required by law. We do not share any individual user information with any of our business partners or outside vendors without permission. We may share aggregated statistics with business partners or outside vendors without permission.

We use a billing processing company to bill users for some goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Billing information will be retained internally by Feedster as required by law.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Feedster, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users, when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Email Alerts**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to any of our email alerts, we ask them to register by providing their contact information (name and email address) and to create a username and password and to opt-in for the email alerts.

**Opt-In and Unsubscribe**  
Feedster subscribers are given the opportunity to 'opt-in' to having their information used for purposes not directly related to our website at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line of the email or by emailing remove AT SIGN feedster.com.

Users of our Web site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

Feedster reserves the right to remove members. Feedster will notify the deleted member through that user's email address of this action, or will make best efforts to do so, to explain why this action was taken.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Feedster does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Feedster and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Questionnaires**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via questionnaires. Participation in these questionnaires is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and contact address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Information will be used internally for purposes of monitoring or improving use of and satisfaction with this Web site. Survey information will only be shared outside the company in the form of aggregated statistics.

**Offers**  
Feedster sends all new subscribers a welcoming email to verify password and username. Current subscribers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter if they opt-in to this service. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see description of our choice/opt-in policy below.

**Site Updates and New Features Announcements**  
Feedster sends subscribers administrative site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe or opt-out from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user regarding updates to our site and service and issues relating to their account via email (or phone for billing issues).

**Security and Confidentiality**  
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except as required by law or other regulation.

**Correcting/Updating/Removing Personal Information**  
Feedster collects traffic data in logs and this information is maintained indefinitely. For subscribers (including those using our developer tools): if a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove that member's personal data. Information collected for the membership process, if requested, will be deleted within 10 days from the website. To notify Feedster of a change, you can send email to: support AT SIGN feedster.com. However, some personal information may need to be maintained if it is connected with billing information or as required by law.

Feedster reserves the right to delete members from the site. Feedster will notify the deleted member through that user's email address of this action, or will make best efforts to do so, to explain why this action was taken.

**Notification of Changes**  
Feedster reserves the right to change this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email, with the option to opt-in to the new policy within 30 days. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
